原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     小酸奶   苏小黛   一只虾
翻译     吃冰棒   TheWalkingNerd
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     没有影子
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
双峰
第三季 第十二集
谢天谢地戈登在他的酒窖里储备了刨子
Thank God Gordon stocks the plane from his own wine cellar.
不  你去告诉她
No, you'll be the one to tell her.
别理会这个怪人
Ignore the strange man.
-敬联调局  -敬联调局
- Here's to the bureau. - To the bureau.
敬联调局
To the bureau.
艾伯特
Albert.
戈登
Gordon.
好了  现在说说你需要知道的事
Okay, here's what you need to know.
拜托说得简洁点
Please speak succinctly,
别发出任何尖锐的噪音
and do not make any loud, sharp noises.
1970年  美国空军终止了蓝皮书计划
In 1970, the United States Air Force shut down Project Blue Book,
即他们对不明飞行物为期二十年的调查
their 20-year investigation into UFOs.
他们得出结论  没有可靠证据存在
They concluded that no credible evidence existed
因此他们认为不明飞行物对国家安全没有威胁
and therefore they posed no threat to national security.
换句话说  是个巨大的掩饰
In other words, a massive cover-up.
干杯
Cheers.
几年后  军方和联调局
A few years later, the military and FBI
组建了一支高度机密的特遣部队
formed a top secret task force
去探索蓝皮书没能解答的
to explore the troubling abstractions
令人不安的抽象概念
raised by cases Blue Book failed to resolve.
我们称之为蓝色玫瑰
We called it the Blue Rose after a phrase
这是那些案件中的一个女人
uttered by a woman in one of these cases
临死前说出的一个词
just before she died
暗示着我们永远无法企及这些答案
which suggested these answers could not be reached
除非通过我们从未踏足过的另一条途径
except by an alternate path we've been traveling ever since.
戈登推荐了一位名叫菲利普·杰弗里斯的探员
Gordon suggested an agent by the name of Phillip Jeffries
作为队长
to head the squad.
他很快招募了另外三人
He soon recruited three others:
我  切特·戴斯蒙德和戴尔·库柏
myself, Chet Desmond, and Dale Cooper.
也许你已经注意到了
Perhaps you haven't failed to notice
我是那组人里
that I'm the only one of that group
唯一没有无故消失的
who hasn't disappeared without explanation,
所以戈登也迟迟没有向我们团队中
which has led to a certain reluctance on Gordon's part
注入新鲜的血液
to bring new blood into the fold...
直至今晚
until tonight.
普雷斯顿探员
Agent Preston,
我们关注你很久了
you've been on our radar
你在华盛顿高中上了荣誉榜
since you made the honors list at George Washington High,
还是麻省理工的年度优秀学生
not to mention the dean's list at MIT
并在匡提科名列前茅
and top of your class at Quantico.
你们想让我加入蓝色玫瑰特遣队
You're asking me to join the Blue Rose task force.
没错
Yep.
我加入
I'm in.
明早我跟你简单介绍具体情况
I'll brief you in detail in the morning.
好的
Okay.
敬塔米和蓝色玫瑰
To Tammy and the Blue Rose.
敬蓝色玫瑰
The Blue Rose.
戴安在路上了
Diane's on her way.
请坐 戴安
Have a seat, Diane.
喝一杯吗
Care for a drink?
我喜欢冰镇的
I like it on the rocks.
你运气好
Well, you're in luck.
达科他还是冰天雪地的季节
The Dakotas are still in the Ice Age.
戴安
Diane,
我们你知道你跟库柏探员的合作
we know your work with Agent Cooper has given you
让你对蓝色玫瑰有了较深了解
more than a passing insight into the Blue Rose.
即便你已经不是局里的人了
Even though you're no longer a part of the bureau,
我们还是想当你的代理人
we'd like to deputize you.
只是暂时的
On a temporary basis,
我们真的需要你的帮助
because we really need your help.
我有什么好处
What's in it for me?
现金
Some cash.
不太多
Not much.
或许还有查清你朋友库柏
Maybe the satisfaction of learning
究竟遭遇了什么的满足感
what happened to your friend Cooper.
那就开始吧
Let's rock.
能给我一盒塞勒姆香波吗  谢谢
Uh, could I have a carton of Salems, please?
牛肉干
多少钱
How much is it?
133块7
$133.70.
我不记得那里之前有牛肉干
I don't remember seeing those beef jerky there before.
是新到的货
Uh, that's new.
什么口味的
What type is it?
是火鸡  不是牛肉
Uh, it's turkey, not beef.
是烟熏口味的吗
Is it smoked?
我猜是吧
Uh, I-I think so.
这个跟牛肉干是一样的
It's the same as beef jerky,
只不过是火鸡肉而已
except it's made from turkey.
第一次入这货的时候你在吗
Were you here when they first came?
在
Uh, yes.
这是他们几周前进的货
They brought it in a couple weeks ago.
你这里有点不对劲
Your room seems different.
有人来了
And men are coming.
我
Uh, I'm...
我...我不是很懂你在说什么
I'm-I'm not sure I know what you mean.
我在提醒你们要当心
I am trying to tell you that you have to watch out!
大祸将至
Things can happen!
曾经降临在我头上的大祸
Something happened to me.
Something happened to me!
我有点难受  我不舒服
I don't feel good. I don't feel good.
我不舒服
I don't feel good.
I don't feel good!
萨拉
Sarah.
萨拉  停...  停手
Sarah, s-stop doing this.
我要不要叫医生
Should-should I call a doctor?
停手  快停手
Stop doing this. Stop doing this.
好的  离开这里
Okay. Leave this place.
找车匙  找车匙
Find the car key. Find the car key.
拿车匙
Get the car key.
拿车...  快拿车匙
Get the car-- get the goddamn car key!
什么啊
What?
我...
I...
我知道她住哪
I know where she lives.
我可以把这些送过去给她
I can d-deliver them.
我猜
I guess.
上午九点半  不可提前  到下午五点半
克里斯克尔
Kriscol.
我想问你点事
I want to ask you something.
你又去卖血了吗
You been selling your blood again?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
克里斯克尔
Now, Kriscol,
你上周是不是帮杰金斯装了煤气罐
did you install a new propane tank for Jenkins last week?
没错  先生
Yes, sir.
你有收钱吗
Did you get paid for that?
没有  先生
No, sir.
你有没有修剪和清理草坪
Do you mow lawns around here and rake up?
有  先生
Yes, sir.
那你有拿报酬吗
Do you get paid for that?
没有  先生
No, sir.
那好  克里斯克尔
Okay, Kriscol.
这五十美元是给你报酬
Here's 50 bucks for the work.
还有  你这个月不用付我房租
Plus don't pay me for any rent this month.
-什么  -房租快到期了
- What? - Rent is due soon.
不过这个月不要付房租
Don't pay it this month.
还有下次你还想要卖血的话
And the next time you're thinking about selling your blood,
过来跟我说
come talk to me about it.
我并不喜欢这行为
I don't like it.
我不喜欢靠卖血为生的人
I don't like people selling their blood to eat.
虽说医院的病人需要别人献血
It's true the hospital medical people need people to donate blood,
但你已经献得够多了
but you've given enough already.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
保存好你的血  克里斯克尔
Keep your blood, Kriscol.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
你好  萨拉
Hello, Sarah.
霍克
Hawk.
一直想来找你
Been meaning to stop by.
有些旧案子的问题  我想到了你
Some old cases popped up, and I thought about you.
那你真好
That's very kind of you,
不过我猜你来
but I suppose you're really here
是为了杂货店发生的事吧
because of what happened in the grocery store.
是的  我听说了
Yeah, I heard about that.
他们都很担心你
Uh, people were worried about you.
我也不知道自己怎么了
I just don't know what came over me.
不过你现在没事了
But, uh, you're okay now.
我挺好的
I feel fine now.
-屋子里还有谁吗  -没有
- Is somebody in the house? - No.
没有  只是厨房里有些东西而已
No, just something in the kitchen.
你没事吧
You're okay, then.
这是个很糟糕的故事  对吧  霍克
It's a goddamn bad story, isn't it, Hawk?
萨拉  如果你需要帮忙
Sarah, if you need any help,
有任何需要
if you need anything,
给我打电话  好吗
I want you to call, okay?
我是说真的
I mean it.
任何帮助
Help of any kind.
谢谢你  霍克
Thanks, Hawk.
未知号码
拉斯维加斯吗
他们还没有说
-打搅一下  -什么事
- Excuse me. - Hmm?
杜鲁门警长来了
Sheriff Truman is here.
好  请他进来
Yeah, please, have him come in.
弗兰克
Frank.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
最近还好吗
How are you?
请坐
Have a seat.
好
Yeah.
这个...
So...
有什么我可以帮你的吗
What can I do for you?
有点难以启齿  本
There's no easy way to say this, Ben.
是你的孙子理查德
Your grandson Richard
撞死了那个小男孩并逃逸了
was the one who ran over and killed that little boy.
天呐
Oh, my God.
理查德
Richard.
他好像还试图
And it looks like he tried
杀死本案的唯一目击者
to kill the only witness who saw him do it.
米里亚姆·沙利文
Miriam Sullivan.
一名幼教
Nursery school teacher.
她现在还在重症监护中
She's in intensive care.
没有保险
No insurance.
她现在急需手术
Desperately needs an operation.
我希望你能...
I was hoping that you could--
当然  当然
Of course. Of course.
费用由我来出
I'll take care of it.
理查德
Richard.
那个孩子就没做过什么好事
That boy has never been right.
很抱歉把这个坏消息告诉你
Sorry to have to bring you this news.
哈里  你弟弟
Harry, your brother,
已经抓过理查德好几次了
has had a number of run-ins with Richard.
也不是什么重罪
Nothing too bad,
只是每次都比上次要严重  还有....
but each time was worse than the time before, and...
哈里知道这件事吗
Does Harry know about this?
知道了
Yeah.
我们一直有联系
We stay in touch.
那理查德他...  他在哪  进监狱了吗
And Richard is-- Where is he? Is he in jail?
他还在逃逸中
He's on the run.
如果你有他的消息...
If you hear from him--
我不这么认为
Oh. I doubt that.
自从我拒绝再给他钱后
We pretty much lost contact
我们就基本上没联系了
when I refused to give him more money.
哈里怎么样了
How's Harry?
还撑得住
He's hanging in there.
当然  我们还是保持乐观
Course, we're hoping for the best.
当然
Of course.
那个女孩呢
And that girl?
她在这里的医院吗
Is she in the hospital here?
是的
Yeah.
在重症监护病房里
Intensive care?
是的
Yeah.
那那个小男孩的父母呢
And the boy's parents?
可想而知吧
As you can imagine.
我准备把这个寄给哈里
I was going to send this to Harry.
什么
What's that?
这把钥匙
The key here.
前几天随着邮件寄给我的
Showed up in the mail the other day.
我们近二十年来都没用过这种钥匙了
We haven't used a key like this in over 20 years.
315房
Room 315.
我很肯定这就是库柏特工
I'm pretty sure that this is the key
原来住的房间的钥匙
to Agent Cooper's old room.
我觉得哈里会想留个纪念
I thought Harry would like to have it as a memento.
你觉得他会吗
You think he would?
会
Yeah.
会的  本
Yeah, Ben.
你想我把这个带给他吗
You want me to take it for him?
好
Yeah.
你觉得他会喜欢吗
You think he would like it?
会的
Yeah.
很有意思
Interesting.
我们正好有个新案子和库柏特工有关
We're just opening up an old case involving Agent Cooper.
奇怪...
Strange...
过了这么多年这把钥匙突然冒了出来
this key shows up after all these years.
是啊
Yeah.
我也这么觉得
I thought so too.
我真的觉得他会喜欢的
I really think he would like it.
这会对他很有意义
It'd mean a lot to him.
抱歉  本  给你带来了这样一个坏消息
I'm sorry, Ben, to bring you this news.
很高兴再见到你
Good to see you again.
真希望不是因为这种事来找你
Wish it was under better circumstances.
没事
Yeah.
如果有他的消息  我会告诉你的
I'll let you know if, uh... if I hear from him.
我们有了新进展也会通知你的
I'll let you know if we have more news.
谢谢你  弗兰克
Thanks, Frank.
给哈里
For Harry.
理查德
Richard,
我的孙子
my grandson,
杀死了那个小男孩
killed that little boy.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
理查德生下来就没有父亲
Richard never had a father.
我记得...
I remember...
我记得怎么骑自行车
I remember riding.
我父亲给了我一辆旧施文自行车...
My father got me this old Schwinn...
二手的
...secondhand.
他把它漆成了绿色
He painted it green,
安了一个新坐板
got a new seat for it.
两种绿色  有点儿...
Two-tone green, kind of a...
柠檬绿和深丛林绿混在一起
kind of a lime green and a deep forest green.
轮胎很大
Fat tires.
好难骑
Oh, it was so hard to ride,
但我很喜欢那辆自行车
but I loved that bike.
我很喜欢那辆自行车
I loved that bike.
我和我的朋友一起骑自行车
I'd ride with my friends.
打给医院
Call the hospital.
把她的费用都结清了  米里亚姆...
I want you to arrange to pay for all of Miriam, uh...
我记不清她姓什么了
I don't even remember her last name,
但他们会知道是谁的
but they'll-they'll know who she is.
米里亚姆的所有医疗费用
All of Miriam's medical expenses.
理查德袭击了她
Richard assaulted her.
她需要做手术
She needs an operation.
贝弗莉  请马上去办
Beverly, please take care of this right away.
好  没问题
Yeah, of course.
我马上去办
I'll do it right now.
我特别喜欢那辆自行车
I loved that bike.
我很喜欢那辆自行车
I loved that bike
那是我父亲送给我的
that my father got for me.
陷阱已经布好了
The trap was set.
他们等待着午夜过后
They waited till after midnight,
然后75名壮汉翻过这座山
and then, 75 strong, they came up over the mountain,
警笛哀嚎  拔枪布阵
sirens wailing, guns drawn--
艾伯特
Albert.
戈登
Gordon,
你能要你的朋友到楼下等候吗
would you please ask your friend to wait downstairs?
亲爱的  你能让我们单独待会儿吗
Sweetheart, would you excuse us for a moment?
我到酒吧打给你
I'll call you in the bar.
好的  亲爱的
Oui, mon chéri.
很别致
Très chic.
太好喝了
Très bon.
这是好酒
It's a good one.
到了酒吧打给你
Call you at the bar.
她来这拜访一位她母亲的朋友
She's here visiting a friend of her mother
她女儿失踪了
whose daughter has gone missing.
她拥有一座萝卜地
The mother owns a turnip farm.
我要她告诉那位母亲
I told her to tell the mother
她女儿最后会出现的
that her daughter will turn up eventually.
她也没听懂
She didn't get it either.
她是法国人  语言不通
Being French, it doesn't translate.
你明白了吗  艾伯特
Do you realize, Albert,
如今地球上有超过六千种语言
that there are more than 6,000 languages spoken on Earth today?
什么事  艾伯特
What is it, Albert?
戴安收到了这样的短信
Incoming to Diane:
"拉斯维加斯吗"
"Las Vegas?"
她回道"他们还没说"
Outgoing: "They haven't asked yet."
我们还有什么没有跟她说的
What do we know that we haven't asked her about?
会知道的
We'll figure it out.
但目前  我真的很想继续享用
But for now, I'd really like to get back to
这瓶上等的波尔多葡萄酒
this fine Bordeaux.
什么酒
What kind is it?
11点05分
1105.
艾伯特
Albert...
你有时候真令我担心
...sometimes I really worry about you.
你确定吗
You sure?
我确定
I'm sure.
没时间折磨他了  宝贝
We don't have time for torture, babe.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
刚刚路过一家温迪汉堡
Passed a Wendy's back there.
开枪打死他就对了
Just shoot him.
好  没问题
Okay, I'm there.
我可以打他的腿
I can shoot him in the legs.
咱们绑架他
We kidnap him.
这样你就能折磨他
Then you could torture him.
我说过  我饿了
Told you, I'm hungry.
我就确认一下
Just making sure.
他来了
He's here.
爸爸
Daddy!
Daddy.
下一站  温迪汉堡
Next stop, Wendy's.
爸爸
Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy!
爸爸
七点了
It's seven o'clock.
你知道自由在哪吗
Do you know where your freedom is?
A号广播电台为您带来现场直播
Coming to you live and electrified from studio A,
来自美国兴都库什山的
high atop the escarpments of White Tail Peak,
屋脊
the roof-- ruff, ruff--
白尾峰峭壁之巅的声音
of the American Hindu Kush,
这里是安普博士
this is Dr. Amp
唱响独立的颂歌
doing the vamp for liberty,
爬上正义的巅峰
climbing the ramp to justice,
点亮自由的灯火
and lighting the lamp of freedom.
那么
So...
你们今天晚上都在想些什么呢
what's on your mind tonight?
你知道我会讲我在想什么
I mean, you know I'm gonna tell you what's on mine.
我们正在陷入深深的泥潭
We're sinking down deep in the mud.
立刻行动起来
Act now!
朋友们
Friends,
我们都生活在泥潭里
we all live in the mud.
在一摊屎里
In the shit!
快把自己从屎里铲出来
Shovel your way out of the shit.
用这把亮闪闪的金铲子
This is your shiny gold shovel.
双层漆  质量保证
Two coats, guaranteed.
帮你从屎里脱身
Shovel your way out of the shit
来迎接真理
and into the truth.
对我很有帮助  安普博士
It's working for me, Dr. Amp.
从屎坑脱身  只要二十九块九九
Dig yourself out of the shit--$29.99.
没错
That's right.
只要二十九块九九  不包邮
Only $29.99 plus shipping.
安普博士牌
金色屎铲
概不退换
Accept no substitute.
欲购从速
Get yours now.
那帮混蛋又来了
And the fucks are at it again!
那些巨大的跨国企业
These giant multinational corporations
全都是邪恶的害虫
are filled with monstrous vermin,
恶毒卑鄙的杀人凶手
poisonous, vile murderers,
他们吃喝拉撒的都是钱
and they eat, drink, and shit money.
他们廉价收买政客
They buy our politicians for a song.
政客夜夜笙歌  百姓水生火热
Then these fucking politicians sing as we gag and cough,
被政府出卖  只能等死
sold down the river to die.
去你那些被选举出来帮助人民
Fuck you who betray the people you were elected to help,
改善人民生活
elected to work to help
却背叛了人民的政客
to make life better for.
我操死你们  卖国的傀儡
Fuck you all in the ass, you fucking treasonous puppets!
十八层炼狱会迎接你们
The ninth level of hell will welcome you.
够了  我不想再痴等着电话响
Okay, I'm tired of waiting for the phone to ring.
我要去酒馆
I'm going to the Roadhouse.
我知道他讨厌那个地方
I know he couldn't stand that place,
但其他地方我们已经找遍
but we've checked everywhere else.
你要和我一起去吗
Are you coming with me?
奥黛丽  瞧瞧我这些文件
Audrey, look at this paperwork I have,
我急着要处理
and I've got a deadline.
你瞧  堆积如山
Look, stacks of it.
我怎么能放下工作  深夜出门
How can I leave this and go out so late at night?
我也和你一样想找到比利  但...
I want to find Billy same as you, but...
不能明天一早再开始吗
can't we start out in the light of day?
今晚新月  外面漆黑一片
It's a new moon tonight. It'll be dark out there.
留下来  睡个好觉
Stay here and get a good sleep,
明天我们一起去找
and we'll both go looking tomorrow.
怎么有你这种混账
What kind of shit are you?
如果你失踪了
If you were missing,
你希望别人先做完他们该死的作业
would you want people finishing their fucking homework
再去找你吗
before they went looking for you?
你就是一个没种的窝囊废
You're nothing but a spineless, no-balls loser.
你自己知道吗
Do you know that?
知道吗  因为你真的就是这种人
Do you? Because that's what you really are.
奥黛丽
Audrey,
我有截止日期
I have a deadline.
我不得不做
I have to do this.
为什么要因为我尽自己的本分而批评我
Why do you put me down for doing my allotted duty in life?
比利在外头某处
Billy is out there somewhere,
但你今晚也找不着他的
but you're not gonna find him tonight.
我敢保证
I guarantee it.
你很肯定哦
Oh, you know for certain.
你是读了哪一颗水晶球的预言呢
What fucking crystal ball are you looking into?
怎么不向你的水晶球问卜
Why don't you ask your crystal ball
失踪两天的比利
where the fuck Billy is,
到底在哪里
who's been missing for two days?
问你的球啊
Ask your ball.
别这样  奥黛丽
Come on, Audrey.
你知道我没有水晶球
You know I don't have a crystal ball.
已经很晚了  我也困了
It's already late, and I'm getting sleepy.
我睡前还有好多工作要做
I have so much more work to do before I get to sleep.
该死的可怜虫
You poor fucking thing.
我说过  别用这口气跟你老公说话
I told you, don't talk that way to your husband.
我一直对你很好
I've been good to you.
你总是说
You always say it,
我对你有多好
how I've been good to you.
那又怎样
Who cares?
怎么
What?
你要我无时无刻感激你
I got to thank you every hour on the hour,
每天跪拜你吗
get on my knees and adore you?
奥黛丽  我不喜欢你这种语调
Audrey, I don't like the tone of your voice.
查理
Look, Charlie,
咱们直话直说吧
let's just call a spade a spade.
你没种
You have no balls.
所以我才爱上比利
That's why I'm in love with Billy.
所以我才操比利
That's why I am fucking Billy.
奥黛丽
Audrey.
我昨晚梦见比利了
I saw Billy in my dream last night,
他的鼻孔和嘴巴都在流血
and he was bleeding from the nose and mouth.
有时候梦境会反映现实
And dreams sometimes hearken a truth.
我得走了  查理
Now, I got to go, Charlie.
我寻求你的陪伴
I asked for your company,
你的保护
your protection,
但你这胆小鬼
but you're such a milquetoast,
要保护也是我保护你
the only protection would be me protecting you.
还有蒂娜
And Tina--
我得去找蒂娜
I got to find Tina.
她是最后一个见到比利的人
She was the last person to see Billy,
而我受不了和她在同一屋檐下
and I can't fucking stand being in the same room with her.
你该打给她的  你从来不打
You were supposed to call her, but you never did.
别冲我发脾气了  奥黛丽
Don't be sore at me, Audrey.
你知道我只是为你好
You know I just want the best for you.
是吗
Yeah?
那就在我给你的文件上签字
Well, then sign the papers I gave you.
这我不确定  奥黛丽
Uh, I don't know, Audrey.
那些文件
Those papers...
似乎有点不靠谱
there's something fishy about them.
没经过我的律师审阅我不会签字
I'm not signing anything until I run them by my lawyer.
我懂了
Oh, I see.
那或许我该让保罗帮我看一看
Maybe I should run them by Paul.
或许我该请保罗来探望你
Maybe I should have Paul come give you a visit.
不  奥黛丽
Don't, Audrey.
别这样
Don't be like this.
我是你合法的丈夫
I'm your lawfully wedded husband.
我有权利
I have rights.
你放弃这些权利了
You gave up those rights.
什么
What?
你意思是要反悔我们的合约吗
You mean you'd go back on our contract?
你要违约吗
Renege on a contract?
我会这么做的
That's what I will do.
我正打算这么做
That's what I'm doing.
好吧  奥黛丽
Okay, Audrey.
我和你一起去
I'll go with you.
我好困  但我会陪你去
I'm so sleepy, but I'll go.
我们要去哪
Where are we going?
我们要去酒馆
We're going to the Roadhouse.
我跟你说了
I told you.
奥黛丽
Oh, Audrey.
那我去
I'll go, then.
我需要我的外套
I'll need my jacket.
我看你已经穿上你的了
I see you've already got yours.
当然了  不然你以为呢
Uh, yeah, what the fuck do you think?
我跟你说了我们要出去
I told you we were going out.
我显然需要我的外套
Obviously I'll need my jacket.
去外面要穿过一大片的林子
There's thousands of square miles of woods out there, Audrey.
我们就这么走出去
Do you think we're just gonna walk out the door
或者就这么冲到酒馆里
or waltz into the Roadhouse and presto,
他肯定就在吗
there he'll be?
赶紧去拿你的外套
Just get your jacket.
混蛋
Asshole.
等等
Wait a minute.
蒂娜
Tina.
让我给她打个电话  好吗
Let me call her now, okay?
我会告诉她我是一个人  但是...
I know, I'll tell her I'm alone, but...
我们看看她是不是知道些什么
let's see if she knows anything.
如果她丈夫在那里  她就说不了什么  但...
If her husband's there, she won't be able to talk, but...
我们试试
let's see.
好吗
Okay?
好啊  打给这贱人  看看她知道些什么
Okay, call the bitch. See what she knows.
假设她是最后一个见到比利的人
Supposedly she was the last one to see Billy,
但我觉得查克疯疯癫癫的
but I think Chuck is certifiable,
所以他的话我们不能全信
so we can't count on shit from him.
查克告诉你蒂娜是最后一个见到比利的人
Chuck told you Tina was the last person to see Billy?
是的
Yeah.
你知道查克上周偷走了比利的车吗
Did you know that Chuck stole Billy's truck last week?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
比利从家里出来
Billy came out of his house
看到查克开着他的车走了
and saw Chuck driving off with his truck.
然后呢
And?
然后比利找了警长
And Billy called the sheriff.
然后呢
And?
那天下午他们就找到了那辆车
And they found the truck that same afternoon.
那然后呢
So what happened, then?
他们就联系了比利
They called Billy,
我猜比利找回了车  没有提出控诉
and I guess Billy got his truck back and dropped any charges.
真的吗
Really?
好吧
Okay.
打给蒂娜
Call Tina.
我太累了  奥黛丽
I'm so tired, Audrey.
喂
Hello?
蒂娜  我是查理
Yes, Tina. It's Charlie.
你好吗
How are you?
是吗
Yeah?
我知道
Yeah, I know.
不好意思这么晚才打给你
Sorry to call so late.
我想问你点事情
I wanted to ask you something.
好吗
Okay?
查克告诉我
Yeah, so Chuck told me
你可能是最后一个见到比利的人
you might have been the last person to see Billy.
是真的吗
Is this true?
什么
What?
我知道
Yeah, I know that.
你确定吗
You're sure?
但是...
But...
好吧
Okay.
好
Yeah.
是的  蒂娜
Yes, Tina.
好的
Okay.
你怎么知道...什么
How did you find-- What?
真的吗
Really?
我的天啊
Oh, my goodness.
谢谢你  蒂娜
Thank you, Tina.
好
Great.
我们回头再说
I'll talk to you soon.
我明天联系你
I'll try tomorrow.
嗯  还是要为这么晚才联系你道歉
Yeah, again, sorry to call so late.
你跟我说的这些简直难以置信
Unbelievable, what you're telling me.
我不会的
I won't.
快...
Come...
我保证
I promise.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
再见
Bye.
你不会告诉我她说了什么
You're not gonna tell me what she said?
查理
Charlie!
我知道你们关门了
I know you're closed.
谢谢
Thanks.
坐标
Coordinates.
坐
"Co...or...
标
din...ates...
加二
plus two."
双峰镇
枪炮酒吧
安琪拉在哪里
Where's Angela?
我不知道
I haven't got a clue.
她昨晚说好要来的
She was supposed to show last night.
但她也没有出现
She didn't show then either.
她可能在和克拉克一起
She might be with Clark.
克拉克
Clark?
是啊
Yeah.
他们最近总是在一起
They've been hanging out lately.
真的吗
Really?
是啊
Yeah.
你看起来很惊讶
You look surprised.
是啊  因为我大概两个晚上前还看到
Yeah, 'cause I saw Clark and Mary together here,
克拉克和玛丽一起在这里
like, two nights ago.
我很她
I hate her.
安琪拉也恨她
And Angela fucking really hates her too.
他们在这里干什么
What were they doing?
就是在亲热
Like, practically making out.
慢摇  靠得非常近
Slow dancing and getting real close.
就在那个角落
Over in the corner.
沉浸在他们的世界里
Off in their own world.
很多人都看到他们了
Lots of people saw 'em.
要是安琪拉知道了  肯定会气疯了
Angela's gonna go crazy when she gets wind of this.
她对克拉克很认真
She's getting really serious about Clark.
她喜欢他好几周了
He's been on her for a couple of weeks now.
她甚至还会梦到他
She's even dreaming about the guy.
操
Shit.
看来克拉克就是在广撒网
I guess Clark's spreading it around.
她现在还停药了
And she's off her meds now.
我希望克拉克别惹出什么乱子
I hope Clark doesn't fuck this up.
我觉得她肯定接受不了
She won't be able to take it, I don't think.
是啊
Well, yeah.
她情绪很不稳定
She's kind of on the edge.
谁不会呢
Who wouldn't be?
她妈妈那样死的
Losing her mom like that?
操
Fuck.
我来这里的路上差点被杀了
I almost got fucking killed coming over here.
某个混蛋在路上朝我冲过来
Some fucking ass-eater's heading toward me on the highway
把我别出了主路
and runs me off the road.
我就看到两盏大灯冲着我
All I see is two headlights coming fucking right at me.
我驶离了道路  差点撞上一棵树
I drove off the road and almost hit a tree.
还是一个农民把我从车里拉出来的
Some farmer had to pull me out.
该死  真想把那个肇事的家伙杀了
Man, I could kill the motherfucker that did that.
我需要瓶啤酒  你们肯定也要加
I need a beer. Obviously you want one too.
-要加一瓶吗  -好的
- Do you want another one? - Yeah, sure.
好的  我马上回来
All right, I'll be right back.
谢了  特里克
Thanks, Trick.
感觉特里克能捡回一条命真是走运
Trick's lucky to be alive, sounds like.
是啊
Sure does.
特里克不是被软禁了吗
By the way, isn't Trick under house arrest?
没有啊  我是说  这件事已经过去
No. I-I mean, yeah, but he got that behind him now.
他又自由了
He's a free man again.
自由人
A free man.